Guide to the Victor Rabinowitz Papers TAM.123
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Subject Files, 1929-2003.
  - Rabinowitz, Victor: FOIA File (FBI) (X), undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Rabinowitz, Victor: FOIA File (FBI) (XI), undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Rabinowitz, Victor: FOIA File (FBI) (XII), undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Rabinowitz, Victor: FOIA File (FBI) (XIII), undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Rabinowitz, Victor: FOIA File (FBI) (XIV), undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Rabinowitz, Victor: FOIA File (FBI) (XV), undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Rabinowitz, Victor: FOIA File (FBI) (XVI), undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Rabinowitz, Victor: FOIA File (FBI) (XVII), undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Rabinowitz, Victor: FOIA File (FBI) (XVIII), undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Rabinowitz, Victor: FOIA File (FBI) (XIX), undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Rabinowitz, Victor: FOIA File (FBI) (XX), undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Rabinowitz, Victor: FOIA File: Correspondence and Miscellaneous Documents, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Ramparts Magazine, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Reichbach, Gustin, 1971, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Robeson Conference (American Immigration Lawyers Association), 1991 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Rosenberg Case, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Rosenberg, Julius: Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) File (FBI), 1950-1953 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Schulberg, Budd: East Hampton Star Letters, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Seamen's Defense Committee: Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) File (FBI), 1956 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Sills, Sam: "Taking Liberties", 2000 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Southern Education and Research Institute, Inc., 1965 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Sovereign Immunity: Boston College Law School Panel on, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Stern, Alfred K.: Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) File (FBI), 1967 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Talladega, AL, 1962-1963 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Teachers Union of the City of New York: Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) File (FBI), 1955-1956, 1961-1964 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Tunick, Irve: "Honey on the Book" (Radio Script about Louis M. Rabinowitz), 1958 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - University of Virginia School of Law: Sokol Colloquium, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Venezuela, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Washington Commonwealth Federation: Kristi Fog Thesis on, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Watkins Case, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Weather Underground Organization, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Weinstein, James, 1972-1977 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - World Federation of Trade Unions, 1954, 1961-1963 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - World Federation of Trade Unions: Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) File (FBI), 1961 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Writings: Articles, undated (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Writings: Articles, 1960-1966 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Writings: Articles, 1971-1974 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Writings: Articles, 1977-1988 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Writings: "Cuba Book", 1989 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Writings: Memoir (I), 1993 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Writings: Memoir (II), 1993 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Writings: Memoir (III), 1993 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Writings: Memoir (IV), 1993 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Writings: Memoir: Later Draft (I), undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Writings: Memoir: Later Draft (II), undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Writings: Memoir: Later Draft (III), undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Writings: Memoir: Later Draft (IV), undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Writings: Memoir: Later Draft (V), undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Writings: "National Lawyers Guild […]" (Correspondence), 1987-1991 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Writings: "National Lawyers Guild" (Research), undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Writings: "The Nationalisation [sic] of Multinationals in Peripheral Economies" (Contributor), 1978 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Writings: Notes/Miscellaneous, undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Writings: Notes/Miscellaneous, 1959-1966 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Writings: Notes/Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Writings: Notes/Miscellaneous, 1977-1989 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Writings: Politics of Law (Contributor), 1997, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Writings: Reviews, undated (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Writings: Reviews, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Writings: Speeches, undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Writings: Verdicts on Lawyers (Contributor), 1975 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Series III: Legal Case Files, 1918-2001.
  - Adler, Harry, and Minerva Feinstein v. Board of Education of the City of New York et al: Back Pay (I), 1961 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Adler, Harry, and Minerva Feinstein v. Board of Education of the City of New York et al: Back Pay (II), 1961 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Adler, Harry, and Minerva Feinstein v. Board of Education of the City of New York et al: Back Pay (III), 1961 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Albertson, Lillie, v. United States of America: Invasion of Privacy (FBI Surveillance), 1984 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Banco Nacional de Cuba v. Chase Manhattan Bank: Default on Loan, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Banco Nacional de Cuba v. Chemical Bank New York Trust Company et al.: Wrongful Appropriation of Funds, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Berman, Leopold et al., v. National Maritime Union et al.: Discrimination (I), 1958-1960 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Berman, Leopold et al., v. National Maritime Union et al.: Discrimination (II), 1958-1960 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Berman, Leopold et al., v. National Maritime Union et al.: Discrimination (III), 1958-1960 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Berman, Leopold et al., v. National Maritime Union et al.: Discrimination (IV), 1958-1960 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Berman, Leopold et al., v. National Maritime Union et al.: Discrimination (V), 1958-1960 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Bill of Rights Foundation (BORF): Beasley, Joseph D.: Family Planning (I), 1974-1976 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - BORF: Beasley, Joseph D.: Family Planning (II), 1974-1976 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - BORF: Bergman, Lowell, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - BORF: Birnbaum Case: Right to Privacy, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - BORF: Cohen, Robert Carl et al., v. Griffin Bell: Freedom of Speech, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - BORF: Hirsch, Arthur "Buzz": Freedom of Speech, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - BORF: Koff, David Richard: Censorship of Blacks Brittanica film, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - BORF: Newton, Huey P.: Black Panthers, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Boudin, Kathy (People of the State of New York v.): Murder in the Second Degree, 1981-1986, 1999-2001 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Braden, Carl and Anne Braden (Kentucky v.): Advocating Sedition, 1954-1957 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Communist Party et al. v. Board of Regents of the State of New York, 1953-1954 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Congress of Industrial Organizations (CIO) et al. v. Florida, 1945 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Cuba: Sabbatino et al. Case, undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Dermody, Joseph v. Louis Hollander et al.: American Labor Party Nomination, 1940-1941 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Dermody, Joseph et al. v. S. Howard Cohen et al.: City Council Election, 1940-1941 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Fraina, Louis C. (United States of America v.): Selective Draft Law, 1918 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Gelb, Abe and Rosalind, to Harold Liskin: Property Sale, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Giese, Frank Stearns v. United States of America: Seditions Activity, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Gilbert, Irving et al. v. Burlington Industries: Severance Day Policy, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Gilbert, Margaret (Commonwealth of Massachusetts v.): Conspiracy to Overthrow the Government, 1954-1956 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Hiss, Alger: United States Court of Appeals (82-6196): In re: Alger Hiss (I), 1982 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Hiss, Alger: United States Court of Appeals (82-6196): In re: Alger Hiss (II), 1982 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Hiss, Alger: United States Court of Appeals (82-6196): In re: Alger Hiss (III), 1982 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Hiss, Alger: United States Court of Appeals (82-6196): In re: Alger Hiss (IV), 1982 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Hiss, Alger: United States Court of Appeals (82-6196): In re: Alger Hiss (V), 1982 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Hiss, Alger: United States Court of Appeals (82-6196): In re: Alger Hiss (VI), 1982 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Hiss, Alger: United States Court of Appeals (82-6196): In re: Alger Hiss (VII), 1982 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Honicker, Jeannine v. Joseph M. Hendrie et al.: Nuclear Energy, 1978-1979 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Industrial Insurance Agents Local 30 and 70 (Met Life v.): Unfair Labor Practices, 1941 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Jenkins, Junesh (State of Louisiana v.): Subversive Activities, 1954-1958 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Kahan, Michael, v. Board of Education of the City of New York: Denial of Tenure (I), 1979-1989 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Kahan, Michael, v. Board of Education of the City of New York: Denial of Tenure (II), 1979-1989 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Keith, Charles Lawrence: Passport Application, 1956, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Kelly, Jeanette: Workmen's Compensation, 1955-1957 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Kennedy, Robert F. v. Victor Rabinowitz and Leonard Boudin: Foreign Agents Registration Act, 1962-1963 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Kent, Rockwell: HUAC Subpoena, 1955-1956 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Kinoy, Arthur: Grand Jury Subpoena, 1970-1972 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Kinoy, Joanne: Grand Jury Matter, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Kirshner, Alfred, v. United States of America et al.: Teacher Pension Benefits, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Kliot, Aranka (aka Aranka Treuhaft): Divorce, 1955-1956 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Lauber, Morris, and Burt Brown v. Philip Cooper: Property Damage, 1955-1956 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Lightfoot, Claude Mack (United States of America v.): Subversive Activities, 1953-1954 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Martin, Lynn, v. Transport Workers Union Local 101: Election, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Martin, Lynn, v. Transport Workers Union Local 101: Election, 1992-1993 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Mins, Leonard v. Joseph R. McCarthy, 1953-1954 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Nash, Julius, and Irving Mauer v. Board of Education of the City of New York: Wrongful Dismissal, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Nash, Malcolm (United States Attorney v.): Military Selective Service Violation, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Nathan, Otto, and Helen Dukas (Princeton University Press v.): Einstein Papers (I), 1980 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Nathan, Otto, and Helen Dukas (Princeton University Press v.): Einstein Papers (II), 1980 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Nelson, Steve (Commonwealth of Pennsylvania v.): Seditious Activity (I), 1950-1956 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Nelson, Steve (Commonwealth of Pennsylvania v.): Seditious Activity (II), 1950-1956 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Nelson, Steve (United States of America v.): Conspiracy to Violate the Smith Act, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Peck, James, v. United States of America: Failure of Duty to Protect, 1982-1985 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Potash, Irving (United States of America v.): Subversive Activities, 1954-1955 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Powell, John William et al. (United States of America v.): Seditious Activities, 1952-1960 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Rabinowitz, Peter et al. v. Board of Junior College District No. 508: Faculty Transfers (American Association of University Professors), 1966-1972 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Rabinowitz, Peter et al. v. Board of Junior College District No. 508: Faculty Transfers (Argument), 1973 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Rabinowitz, Peter et al. v. Board of Junior College District No. 508: Faculty Transfers (Board of Junior College District No. 508 v. Cook County College Teachers Union Local 1600), 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Rabinowitz, Peter et al. v. Board of Junior College District No. 508: Faculty Transfers (Briefs), 1973-1975 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Rabinowitz, Peter et al. v. Board of Junior College District No. 508: Faculty Transfers (Correspondence), 1973-1975 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Rabinowitz, Peter et al. v. Board of Junior College District No. 508: Faculty Transfers (Correspondence Post-Transfer), 1973 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Rabinowitz, Peter et al. v. Board of Junior College District No. 508: Faculty Transfers (Crisis 1971), 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Rabinowitz, Peter et al. v. Board of Junior College District No. 508: Faculty Transfers (Deposition; Shabat), 1973 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Rabinowitz, Peter et al. v. Board of Junior College District No. 508: Faculty Transfers (Deposition), 1973 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Rabinowitz, Peter et al. v. Board of Junior College District No. 508: Faculty Transfers (Faculty Council), 1971-1973 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Rabinowitz, Peter et al. v. Board of Junior College District No. 508: Faculty Transfers (Formal Documents) (I), 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Rabinowitz, Peter et al. v. Board of Junior College District No. 508: Faculty Transfers (Formal Documents) (II), 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Rabinowitz, Peter et al. v. Board of Junior College District No. 508: Faculty Transfers (Formal Documents) (III), 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Rabinowitz, Peter et al. v. Board of Junior College District No. 508: Faculty Transfers (Grievances), 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Rabinowitz, Peter et al. v. Board of Junior College District No. 508: Faculty Transfers (Humanities Department), 1970-1973 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Rabinowitz, Peter et al. v. Board of Junior College District No. 508: Faculty Transfers (Illinois Tenure Act), undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Rabinowitz, Peter et al. v. Board of Junior College District No. 508: Faculty Transfers (Kennedy King Junior College Course Bulletin), 1973 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Rabinowitz, Peter et al. v. Board of Junior College District No. 508: Faculty Transfers (Material Received on Discovery), 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Rabinowitz, Peter et al. v. Board of Junior College District No. 508: Faculty Transfers (Miscellaneous) (I), 1973-1975 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Rabinowitz, Peter et al. v. Board of Junior College District No. 508: Faculty Transfers (Miscellaneous) (II), 1973-1975 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Rabinowitz, Peter et al. v. Board of Junior College District No. 508: Faculty Transfers (Newsletter Article Drafts), 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Rabinowitz, Peter et al. v. Board of Junior College District No. 508: Faculty Transfers (North Central Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools Report on Southwest College), 1971-1974 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Rabinowitz, Peter et al. v. Board of Junior College District No. 508: Faculty Transfers (Other Voices), 1973 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Rabinowitz, Peter et al. v. Board of Junior College District No. 508: Faculty Transfers (Rabinowitz College File), 1973 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Rabinowitz, Peter et al. v. Board of Junior College District No. 508: Faculty Transfers (Rabinowitz Interview), 1973 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Rabinowitz, Peter et al. v. Board of Junior College District No. 508: Faculty Transfers (Relevant Arbitration), 1969-1970 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Rabinowitz, Peter et al. v. Board of Junior College District No. 508: Faculty Transfers (Role of Faculty), 1968-1972 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Rabinowitz, Peter et al. v. Board of Junior College District No. 508: Faculty Transfers (Rules), 1973 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Rabinowitz, Peter et al. v. Board of Junior College District No. 508: Faculty Transfers (Union), 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - RCA Communications v. American Communications Association: Arbitration (I), 1963-1966 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - RCA Communications v. American Communications Association: Arbitration (II), 1963-1966 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - RCA Communications v. American Communications Association: Arbitration (Transcripts), 1965-10-22 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - RCA Communications v. American Communications Association: Arbitration (Transcripts), 1965-12-07 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - RCA Communications v. American Communications Association: Arbitration (Transcripts), Jan 20, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Reems, Harry (United States of America v.): Conspiracy to Transport Obscene Materials across State Lines, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Schenk, Charles T., and Elizabeth Baer (United States of America v.): Conspiracy to Overthrow the Government, 1918 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Snedigar, Richard W., v. Guerry Hoddersen et al.: Freedom Socialist Party, 1984-1989 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Snedigar, Richard W., v. Guerry Hoddersen et al.: Freedom Socialist Party (Clerk's Papers), 1986 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Snedigar, Richard W., v. Guerry Hoddersen et al.: Freedom Socialist Party (Clerk's Papers), 1988 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Snedigar, Richard W., v. Guerry Hoddersen et al.: Freedom Socialist Party (Transcripts), 1985-1987 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Strong, Anna Louise: Passport Application, 1955-1957 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Student Non-Violent Coordinating Committee (SNCC) v. United States of America: Violation of Constitutional Rights, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - SNCC v. USA: Violation of Constitutional Rights: Chicago Police Department Surveillance Files, 1963-09-1965-06 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - SNCC v. USA: Violation of Constitutional Rights: Chicago Police Department Surveillance Files, 1964-07-1965-02 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - SNCC v. USA: Violation of Constitutional Rights: Chicago Police Department Surveillance Files, 1965-03-1967-01 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - SNCC v. USA: Violation of Constitutional Rights: Chicago Police Department Surveillance Files, 1967-02-1967-09 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - SNCC v. USA: Violation of Constitutional Rights: Chicago Police Department Surveillance Files, 1967-09 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - SNCC v. USA: Violation of Constitutional Rights: Chicago Police Department Surveillance Files, 1967-02-1967-11 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - SNCC v. USA: Violation of Constitutional Rights: Chicago Police Department Surveillance Files, 1967-02-1969-08 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - SNCC v. USA: Violation of Constitutional Rights: Chicago Police Department Surveillance Files, Index, undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - SNCC v. USA: Violation of Constitutional Rights: Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - SNCC v. USA: Freedom of Information Act Requests and Documents, 1976, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - SNCC v. USA: Violation of Constitutional Rights: Miscellaneous, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - SNCC v. USA: Violation of Constitutional Rights: Notes, undated (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - SNCC v. USA: Violation of Constitutional Rights: Press, 1963, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - SNCC v. USA: Violation of Constitutional Rights: Research, undated (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - SNCC v. USA: Violation of Constitutional Rights: SNCC Membership, undated (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Walker, Doris Brin: Passport Application, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Wright, Pat, and Jack Lieberman v. Chief of Transit Police et al.: Sale of Socialist Newspapers in Subway, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Wright, Pat, and Jack Lieberman v. Chief of Transit Police et al.: Sale of Socialist Newspapers in Subway (I), 1976 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Wright, Pat, and Jack Lieberman v. Chief of Transit Police et al.: Sale of Socialist Newspapers in Subway (II), 1976 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Wright, Pat, and Jack Lieberman v. Chief of Transit Police et al.: Sale of Socialist Newspapers in Subway, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Yellin, Ed (United States of America v.): HUAC Subpoena, Contempt of Congress, 1958-1961 (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Series IV: Appointment Books, 1943-2001.
  - Appointment Books, 1943-1946, 1962-1965, 1974-1979 (Box 22)
  - Appointment Books, 1980-1989 (Box 23)
  - Appointment Books, 1990-1994, 1997-2001 (Box 24)
- Series V: Records of the Louis M. Rabinowitz Foundation, 1954-1991.
  - Correspondence, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (I), 1960 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (II), 1960 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (I), 1962 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence (II), 1962 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence (I), 1963 (Box 25, Folder 7a)
  - Correspondence (II), 1963 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence (I), 1964 (Box 25, Folder 8a)
  - Correspondence (II), 1964 (Box 25a, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (I), 1965 (Box 25a, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (II), 1965 (Box 25a, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (I), 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (II), 1966 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (I), 1967 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (II), 1967 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (I), 1968 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (II), 1968 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence (I), 1969 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence (II), 1969 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence (I), 1970 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence (II), 1970 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence (III), 1970 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence (I), 1971 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (II), 1971 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (I), 1973 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (II), 1973 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (III), 1973 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence (I), 1974 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence (II), 1974 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence (III), 1974 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence (IV), 1974 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence (V), 1974 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence (VI), 1974 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (I), 1975 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (II), 1975 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (III), 1975 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (I), 1976 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (II), 1976 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Acceptances: A, undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Acceptances: B-BI, undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Acceptances: BL, undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Acceptances: BO, undated (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Acceptances: BR-BZ, undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Acceptances: C-CI, undated (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Acceptances: CO, undated (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Acceptances: D, undated (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Acceptances: E, undated (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Acceptances: F, undated (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Acceptances: G, undated (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Acceptances: H, undated (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Acceptances: I, undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Acceptances: J, undated (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Acceptances: K-KL, undated (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Acceptances: KO-KU, undated (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Acceptances: L-LEN, undated (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Acceptances: LER-LU, undated (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Acceptances: Mc, undated (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Acceptances: MA-ME, undated (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Acceptances: MI-MZ, undated (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Acceptances: NA, undated (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Acceptances: NEW-NY, undated (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Acceptances: O, undated (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Acceptances: P-PE, undated (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Acceptances: PH-PU, undated (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Acceptances: R-RE, undated (Box 31, Folder 4)